=Born Again=
=Episode 14=
What are you doing?
Your teacher told me
you're dropping out of school.
What's the use of going to school?
I don't want to study.
I want to be a star.
I want to make big money.
Big money doesn't come that easily.
You're so annoying.
Xiaotang.
(This is the day.)
(The day I decided to drop out
and run away from home.)
(Not long after that,)
(Mom got sick.)
Xiaotang,
it's okay.
(Streamer Labor Contract)
Sign this contract.
I'll handle your mom's medical bills.
(Streamer Labor Contract)
Xiaotang.
What's wrong with you?
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'll never argue with you again.
This time, I will definitely study hard.
I'll listen to you.
I'll do whatever you say.
Do you realize you're wrong?
And now you'll listen to me?
Do you remember
the oath you swore last night?
You said you wouldn't go to school
even if you were beaten to death.
You told me
that if I kept pushing you,
you would run away from home.
I can't sleep a wink last night.
What tricks are you pulling now?
What do you want now?
Mom, I mean it.
I was so foolish before.
I know you mean well for me.
This time, I will study hard.
Just trust me once.
Trust me one more time.
Xiaotang,
do you really think that way?
Yes, Mom.
I promise
I will definitely study hard this time,
get into a good college,
and find a proper job.
I'll never chase
those star dreams anymore.
I swear.
Silly child.
Alright.
Look at you crying like this.
What a sight.
I'll freshen you up.
Time to go to school.
Let's go.
Go to school.
Wait.
Changed your mind again?
Want to go to school and waste my money?
Don't talk nonsense.
My daughter has grown up.
She wants to study.
Grown up?
I think she just realized
she can't make it out there.
Study?
My foot!
What's the use
of a girl studying so much?
It's better to start working
and earn money early.
I don't have money for her to waste.
Su Dawei, I don't care
if you agree or not.
I'll go out and dig through trash myself
to put my daughter through school.
You wench, how dare you talk back to me?
Seeking a beating?
- Mom!
- I'll beat you to death today!
How dare you defy me!
Su Dawei!
If you dare lay another finger
on my mom,
I won't let you leave here alive.
You brat, how dare you
point a knife at your father?
Father?
A scum like you
doesn't deserve to be my father.
If I remember correctly,
you lost all your wages
at the Card Room in South City,
and borrowed 3,000 yuan
from the loan shark.
Nonsense!
Nonsense?
After you got into debt,
you ran off and disappeared.
I worked to earn money
to help Mom pay for her treatment.
Your creditors caught me
and asked me where you were.
I couldn't answer them,
so they beat me and cursed at me.
The loan shark's rules.
If you don't pay up in three days,
you'd lose a finger.
Today...
Today is the third day, isn't it?
Su Dawei,
the creditors aren't as merciful as me.
Mom.
Don't be afraid. It's okay now.
Heaven has given me this chance
to be back
and protect you.
This time, we will definitely
have a perfect ending.
I promise.
(Since the loop has returned
to seven years ago,)
(this time, I have a chance
to change everything.)
(Su Dawei, that animal!)
(This time,)
(I will never let him hurt my mom.)
(Ye Shen,)
(this time,)
(will you be by my side?)
(Where are you right now?)
Gu Xiaotang,
are you home?
The homeroom teacher sent me.
- (This voice...)
- She said you aren't coming to school.
She's worried about you.
(Fashion)
Gu Xiaotang,
are you home?
The homeroom teacher sent me.
She said you aren't
coming to school anymore.
She's worried about you.
Ye Shen!
Wait a moment.
I'll be right down.
Ye Shen!
(Ye Shen,
fate has given us another chance.)
(This time, I will definitely help you
make up for your regrets.)
(I believe we will definitely
create a perfect ending.)
Gu Xiaotang, what's wrong with you?
Long time no see.
Give me a hug.
The teacher asked me
to tell you to go back to class.
What's wrong with a hug?
Just grant me.
This is a hug for our friendship.
Wait.
We did cleaning together yesterday.
I wiped the blackboard for you.
How is it a long time?
Are you running a fever?
You...
Every loop is like this.
Your memory keeps resetting.
My kindness goes in vain!
Have you read too much sci-fi?
Hey you! Stop it!
Stop right there!
Everyone, you'll have the exam.
Take out your books and review.
Ye Shen, let me tell you...
Gu Xiaotang.
Miss, I've brought Gu Xiaotang back.
(This is real.)
(Right.)
(This time, I have to seize the chance)
(to make up for the regrets
from Ye Shen and me.)
I, Gu Xiaotang,
have officially come back.
The old Gu Xiaotang died yesterday.
Today, you will see
a brand-new Gu Xiaotang.
You will witness with your own eyes
what rebirth from the ashes
means.
Gu Xiaotang, go back to your seat.
The exam is coming.
Hope you can get great scores
like you say.
Okay.
(Go all out,
the promising future is coming)
(128 days left
until college entrance exam)
Alright, do your own exam paper.
Behave.
(Is there anything more terrifying)
(than doing a math exam
right after coming back?)
(My regret)
was in my high school days.
There were some things
that I didn't get to say
or get to do in time.
Thinking back now,
it's all too late.
(What exactly is Ye Shen's regret?)
(Why wouldn't he tell me?)
(Could it be...)
(Could his regret be...)
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪